this is the story of something strange
very strange that happened to me in
minecraft it all started with the chicken
hello chicken oh i have food in my hand oh
have it oh there's a skeleton we run
call me kevin has made the advancement
the parrots and beds wait a second am i being
pranked this is sucks maybe i'm playing as him
look who is getting pranked here when i look
into the mirror and i look like jim pickers
so there i was accidentally stealing
call me kevin's minecraft account if i'm
already here i may as well make this count and
play the entire session as jim pickens welcome
to today's session we are going to be making
a cult i mean community the only way i can
prank kevin is that i do the anti-gym moves he's
a vegetarian now he does not kill he's a pacifist
good news is kevin's got lots of stuff
bad news is if i lose all his stuff
the prank will be pricey now can i place a chest
here even though there are things on the ground
can i put it on those it looks like they are just
glitching in and out look at all this chicken
i think i should stop feeding them because at this
rate we have too many we also used to have llamas
but it is spawned you're just staring at me you
want to go back right okay let's go come with me
come with me no no more of them
are leaving to be fair it's okay
i sleep first make more torches then head to the
cave many many torches so let's head to that cave
i hope i will find a way chicken be good i'll
be back i hope the direction i took oh it hurt
i see it i think this is it look at the size of
this cave i told you it was gonna be dangerous
it's a job for jim he's being a pacifist but
if he gets a tagged he can hit back a self
defense oh my gosh there are already two zombies
there this is very dangerous i better not fall
no way and that's safe oh my gosh that
was brilliant uh the only thing is
i've got company but i think he's gonna be
tagged in a moment oh okay no this is fine
fire is our friend hold space to go up the water
what this is like some magic trick i can use
the water as elevator and i should not fall and
there's a bat too do bats attack i sure hope they
don't because uh i'm a pacifist and i need to eat
some pumpkin pie to stay safe wow you came around
that's how jim defends himself he screams call
me kevin has made the advancement monster hunter
yeah sure it was call me kevin got some
carrots here i was mining the other day
i could barely find a thing oh jim doesn't know
how to swim wait can i not put there the block
here block it block it i feel like i'm
gonna fall don't full jam don't fall
we made it stone cobblestone oh oh there's
a skeleton i heard i heard the arrows
they don't want us to be friends how do i how
do i protect ourselves can i use the shield
oh oh no no no no oh come and kevin has made the
advancement not today i'm protecting ourselves
oh no we've got company oh
i thought i could maybe defend ourselves
we're gonna have to go back and pick our stuff
up but it's night time oh no we need to go back
but now i have nothing what will i do they will
despawn if i don't go back right but it's also
most likely i'm gonna die if i go back let's go
i like a good challenge oh no we need to take
a detour we need to use the elevator to go down
through the water don't hurt yourself
you only have rotten flesh to eat
don't earn yourself jim i told you i don't
think i want to know who these people are
and why are they following me oh is this
such a bad idea this is such a bad idea no
oh there's a torch there there's a torch this
way jimbo's here jim was here jim was there jim
went this way jim went up jim went up here but i
can no longer go up i don't have blocks to go up
oh shoot i'm stuck i'm gonna have to try to
get dirt with my own hands with my bare hands
because i have nothing on me this
is such a horrible idea like does
anyone remember which way to go oh shoot you
should i do remember the water i do remember i
did this maybe i should use this water to go here
okay let's be brave yeah the worst thing we die
man it feels like we have lost all our
progress let's start from zero a sword
oh it's cobblestone and the stick i forgot
i lost all my sticks we also lost our button
we always always need to have a
button on ourselves the unfortunate
truth is that on our bingo card for one of
the files from whichever angle you look at it
the only only place where we could score
five in a row is with a diamond even if i
find diamond i can't mine it until we're gonna
have another iron tool but maybe i'm gonna leave
is there an undo button in minecraft what do i do
this is too much but all these axes they're
gonna be in the xbox haha but i i made a joke out
it was funny right it's not even funny
what's funny about it is how it's not funny
still upstairs there you go oh
there's one right next to our chicken
hello [__] what can i do they're just gonna
explode it the chicken are the chicken are
fighting them off look at them they just have
him completely cornered he's stuck in there what
if i open the gate for him and lead him away he
honestly should leave my chicken alone oh no no no
no they were so brave
i was trying to lead them away there's feather
there's meat jimmy's vegetarian there is no
chicken left inside it's only gym isn't it
fitting isn't it fitting this is not ideal
let's go home boys shall we let's go home
this looks like a battlefield with the arrows
everywhere i'm gonna feed you guys you deserve it
you'll be the first two chicken we have there's
a little chicken already i'm gonna feed them too
oh a new beginning so we are mainly living
off of pumpkin pies oh oh oh oh oh no did
you guys see that i'm scared oh no i'm not here
i did not steal ever in my life anyone's llamas
right now that we have torches maybe it's
it's time to go back to the mine ah what
i just want a bit of a peace of mind i want it
to go mining you need a shield i have a shield
i had a shield where is our
button did i lose the button
i'm looking for iron very important resources
to try to get a diamond oh i see some
iron can you guys see that
down there i think that's it
oh no i don't want to go under the water no
no no just here i don't want to drown here
that would not be funny i need to stay afloat the
water keeps dragging me on the siren yes we found
there's more there no i think i have everything
what's this tunnel like i don't want to drown
oh that's very pretty uh i
don't want to drown oh no panic
oh my gosh and i just need to
find my way home i guess but
um
i was genuinely worried that stuck here forever
for real there was diamonds under the water in
that cave diamonds were like two three blocks
away already found them we just need the iron
pickaxe and then we're gonna complete the
minecraft bingo oh we're gonna have breakfast
before we head back to the mine i've gotta have
breakfast with a beautiful view i was gonna say
go away skeleton i wanted to have breakfast
i think it was this way why is it not this
way goodness me does anyone remember so
don't don't cheat use your braceles we did it
we found the underwater cave try not to drown
i guess is rule number one i need a door here
oh no don't drown in oh i think that's it
that's it i saw it oh but i saw it i saw it
it's from here oh no i'm on the wrong side of the
door wait what don't die anna please don't die
what is going on but breathe in breathe out
is that i can see from here that's it right
we just need a door a door to breathe
place it here door place it why is it not
placing the door goodness me goodness me i
thought i was not gonna be able to do it try to
accomplish the task of not messing this up last
minute i can do it from here i can do
it from my air bubble and that means
nothing wait wait wait where is it
we did it don't join enough don't
try go back to the air bubble go
go back i'm spitting go back to the
air bubble go back to the air bubble
pick up the rest of the diamond shall we
but that's just my that w on the board
it only took us a month jim is so happy he could
not be happier look at him go to stay alive
and pick up the rest of the diamond
because why not they are all here
don't you panic girl maybe i should
go back to my bubble until i can
oh my gosh i almost died wait this is not
the way oh no what no i hate this door it's
not very obvious which side is it okay i
was on the right side but then i panicked
three diamonds and almost died twice for it let
me put that diamond in the box before it's too
late a smart person would hide it when no one
expects it no one would expect diamonds to be in
the xbox right thanks so much for watching this
video i hope you enjoyed it please do give it a
thumbs up if you liked it or comment below what
were some of your favorite mr pickens moments
and subscribe for more non-stealing account
content or actually this was a good prank
right maybe we should do it in the future again
just you let me know about it see you soon bye